You know
Taiwanese people rank third in the world
in terms of vegetarianism
Do you know how many
At least three million or more
They are all vegetarians
Some people are vegetarians
thought ate healthily
Once the health check report comes out
All red
The doctor also said he had sarcopenia
anemia
Osteoporosis and other problems
Ouch, how could this happen?
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I'm your old friend, Dr. Hu.
I want to share this episode with you
Eating vegetarian food makes you fat faster
Don't step on the four major landmines
May cause three highs
Vegetarians are most deficient in protein
This way can stay away from osteoporosis
Being a vegetarian makes you fatter
4 Landmines cause The Three Highs
Vegetarian
The four most common problems
1. Insufficient protein intake
2. Sugar Excess
3. Using the wrong oil
4. Eat lettuce salad
First, insufficient protein intake
We vegetarians
get hungry easily
after eating a meal
The food eat is
Fast digestion
Short feeling of fullness
When hungry
Eating bread is not enough
Come and eat another bun
stomach is full
But what eat
is sugar
and starch
The protein content is low
Not enough protein
The body is prone to fatigue
Slow metabolism
Muscle weakness
Want to replenish physical strength
suggest you eat protein foods instead
Like an egg
Tofu
nut
For example, almond cashews
edamame
You shouldn't eat too little rice at main meals
To maintain
your physical strength
Second, eat too much fruit
Sugar level off the charts.
Are you a fruit lover?
Pay attention
Eat a large bowl of fruit every day
Even eat fruit as a main meal
The sugar content is too high
Not only does blood sugar soar
Excess fructose
It also accumulates in the liver
Fatty liver will occur
in the long run
Third, using the wrong oil
Inflammation in the body can lead to obesity
Some mothers and grandmas
When cooking
Favorite
soybean oil
rapeseed oil
These two are
refined vegetable oils
Especially the food
High temperature stir-frying can easily cause oxidation
It may also produce
trans fats
Eating these oils
for a long time
make you inflamed, fat
and damage your liver.
Blood vessel blockage
So what oil to use?
suggest you use
olive oil
Camellia seed oil
linseed oil
Cooking with low temperature
is healthier
Fourth, love to eat lettuce salad
Want to be energetic
Avoid cold hands and feet
The first step is
Stop eating a lot of cold food
You replace lettuce salad
with hot dishes that have been blanched or stir-fried
Helps warm up the spleen and stomach and nourish qi and blood
The body will warm up
Vegetarians are most deficient in protein
and four nutrients
Is being a vegetarian really healthy?
I have a friend who is in her sixties
and has been a vegetarian for a long time.
husband prepared a vegetarian lunch for him.
Eat at the company
Light and low in oil
Seems healthy, right?
But she often arrives at three o'clock in the afternoon
My stomach started growling
at four o'clock.
even
Occasionally stand up from the chair
legs become weak
Many people think it's because of old age.
In fact, it is insufficient nutrition
What nutrients are often lacking in vegetarians?
There are these five
protein
Vitamin B12
Iron
calcium
and vitamin D
The most likely to be missing
The most important thing that cannot be ignored is
protein
will teach you how to eat right
to make your body strong.
The protein king of vegetables
Beans + it
Improve absorption rate
You keep going every day
But don't know that body
is like a car without gas
The nutrients most likely to be lacking when eating vegetarian food
It's protein
Once it is missing, the whole body will be in trouble
You don't eat enough
Many functions of the body
Like a machine missing parts
It's not running smoothly
Resistance also decreases
After a long time, there will be a lot of small problems
How to supplement protein
for vegetarians
You are a lacto-ovo vegetarian
Eat eggs
milk
These two are the best
They are complete proteins
More complete than plant protein
The absorption rate
is over 90%
You are a vegan
Three types of food
to eat
beans
vegetable
mushrooms
Category 1: Beans
The main force of vegetarians
Tofu
soy milk
edamame
black beans
Especially recommended edamame
50 grams of edamame
Did you know
It has 7 grams of protein
As high as 7 out of 50
A steak about three fingers wide
The size of a three-finger-wide steak
If you eat beans and get bloating easily
You can eat miso bean curd cheese instead
This type of fermented product
Higher absorption rate
More comfortable stomach
Want to improve protein absorption rate
Beans and whole grains
Eat together
Mix edamame with quinoa
Brown rice with tofu
Able to supplement
Essential amino acids for the human body
Helps the body
fully utilize protein
Category 2 Vegetables
The first recommended
It's cauliflower
It is the protein king of vegetables
Every 100 grams of protein
contains 3 to 5 grams.
Nearly as much protein as an egg
Others like cabbage
sweet potato leaves
spinach
baby corn
Green asparagus
The protein content is also good
Category 3: Mushrooms
Eat King Oyster Mushroom
and Hericium erinaceus
mushroom
They are high in protein
Especially King Oyster Mushroom
Known as the steak of the vegetable world
There is also the rare vitamin B12
Usually found in meat
It has
Fracture risk among vegetarians
Twice as many as meat eaters
How to supplement calcium
A study pointed out
It says that compared to meat eaters
Vegetarians and vegans
Generally low bone density
What is the chance of fracture?
More than 31.6%
And people who eat vegan food
The risks are high
The hip fracture rate is 2.31 times
that of meat eaters
Oh, so high
From the perspective of traditional Chinese medicine
the kidney is believed to control bone health and produce marrow
Kidney deficiency leads to weak bones
If calcium is insufficient for a long time
It is equivalent to depleting kidney qi
It affects
more than just bone density
Even memory, hearing,
and waist and leg strength
It might decline.
You are a lacto-ovo vegetarian
How to supplement calcium
Drink one or two glasses of milk every day
yogurt
Or eat cheese
With nuts
Sesame
komutsuna, etc.
Calcium-rich vegetables
Supplement calcium
can get calcium
from six plants without eating dairy products
sweet potato leaves
Chinese kale
Sesame
Nostoc flagelliforme
seaweed
Soybeansproducts
Soybeans are a good source of calcium
Small square dried tofu
and traditional firm tofu
All are highly recommended
But calcium alone isn't enough
It is recommended that you sunbathe
for at least fifteen minutes every day.
With vitamin D
To help calcium absorption
Vegans are prone to B12 deficiency
Deficiency may also be like dementia
Vitamin B12
Severe deficiency
can cause
dementia-like symptoms
Were you here in person
but no longer in spirit?
Many people have poor memory
emotional instability
thought it was because of age
It's actually a lack of vitamin B12
caused by
Reversible dementia
Vitamin B12
It is a nutrient that vegetarians are prone to lacking
Because it almost
Only found in animal foods
The human body cannot synthesize it
When B12 is deficient
What symptoms will the body have?
Chronic anemia
nerve damage
Big mood swings
Decreased concentration
gastrointestinal discomfort
numbness in hands and feet
people who eat lacto-ovo vegetarian food
How to Supplement Vitamin B12
Drink two glasses of milk every day
Combined with other foods
You can meet the standard
Vegan people
Drink plant-based milk with B12
Nutritional yeast powder
If the inspection finds
Insufficient vitamin B12
Don't worry
You can discuss this with your doctor or nutritionist
See if you need to add some egg and dairy foods
in moderation
This makes it easier to replenish
Most importantly
Regular inspections can be performed every year
Check the status of vitamin B12
To avoid anemia
Neurological problems
Memory loss
Let you eat vegetarian food
Healthier
More assured
How to supplement iron most effectively
Iron + 1 substance
The absorption rate increased by 63 percent
Do you often feel
Tired
Difficulty concentrating
Don't rush to blame the pressure
This is likely
body is telling me I'm iron deficient.
Iron deficiency can reduce hemoglobin
Inadequate oxygen delivery
Causes fatigue
asthma
cold hands and feet
Dizziness
Decreased immunity
Severe cases may also affect
work and quality of life
Especially vegetarian friends
Iron deficiency is more likely
Because the absorption rate
of Non-Heme Iron in plants is low
Eating red beans
and spinach alone is not enough
Want to supplement iron
You must choose the right food
Vegetables rich in iron include
Amaranthus gangeticus
Chinese kale
komutsuna
lettuce
And spinach
Iron-containing, bean and grain seeds have
red beans
Butter bean
peanut
pumpkin seeds
black sesame seeds
There is a super secret
Doubles iron absorption
Iron plus vitamin C
European Journal of Nutrition
The study pointed out that
Supplement with vitamin C and prebiotics
Iron utilization
can increase by 43% to 63%
Like
Edamame Quinoa Salad
Add cherry tomatoes
or
Or stir-fried black fungus with Amaranthus gangeticus
With lemonade
Awesome combination
Iron supplementation is not just about eating
Keep it even more
Tea
coffee
calcium
They will take away the iron
Interference absorption
It is recommended to drink it two hours after a meal
Iron and calcium supplements
Four hours interval
The absorption effect is better
What kind of vegetarian food do you eat?
This type of vegetarian diet
may lead to a weak body
What kind of vegetarian food do you eat?
There are four common types of vegetarianism
The first type is vegan, eating only plant-based foods.
The second type: ovo-lacto vegetarian — a vegan diet plus eggs and dairy.
Do not eat meat and wǔ xīn (transliteration)
The third type is wǔ xīn sù(transliteration), which means not eating animal meat.
But eating the wǔ xīn(transliteration) like onions, garlic and leeks
And onions
The fourth type: Guō biān sù (transliteration)
New vegetarians
Will try the Guō biān sù (transliteration)
Pay attention
When eating hot pot with friends
Only eat vegetables and no meat
Seems to eat a lot
In fact, it is easy to lack protein
and iron
Eating vegetarian and wanting to stay healthy
Remember
protein
Good oils
micronutrients
Nothing can be missing
Dear fans,
We have opened the membership channel
If you agree with Dr. Hu's promotion of Chinese medicine
The concept of taking care of your own health
Welcome to support us with a small monthly amount
or become a VIP sponsor
With you
We can go further
Thank you so much